Welcome back.
In this video, we will be talking a
little bit more about Copilot in
Business Central, and we will explore
some additional scenarios. Of course,
Business Central has new Copilot chat,
uh Microsoft Copilot built directly in
Business Central. Uh if you haven't seen
the first video, please do.
In this, we will talk about scenarios.
Let's dive directly into the demo.
So, here I am in Business Central, in
the new version of Business Central.
I can open Microsoft Copilot chat.
I need to set up my sales tax for
Oregon.
Let's ask Copilot.
Copilot pulls data from the internet and
from various other
sources and provides all the answers I
need.
Uh specifically for Oregon, the setup is
uh different than other states
uh because the sales tax rate is zero.
Um let's ask about California.
As you can see, I can continue talking
to Copilot,
asking about different questions, and
actually Copilot provides me even some
suggestions how that conversations might
end up. Where would I go? For instance,
uh
determining a correct uh ZIP codes for
California, and so forth.
That was a very simple uh example, and
it it didn't use Business Central data,
but still it was very useful for
Business Central user.
Let's try another scenario.
In this scenario, we will be asking
Copilot about sales data.
We are looking for items that sold
uh the least in the last 3 months.
Copilot reasons over data. It might It
might take a little bit longer.
And as you can see, Copilot provided me
the answers true to my question.
Specifically, probably the Rome guest
chair
uh and maybe Sydney swivel chair are the
units that sold the least and might
might want to think about how to improve
its ratings. And of course, Copilot
gives me access to those items. It gives
me also some suggestions what to do
next. For instance, suggest actions to
improve
the sales of those slowest items.
In this case, Copilot gives me some
recommendations to bundle those items
together, maybe promote some
underperforming uh color variants, and
cross-sell uh during existing sales. And
I can go and on and on and talk to
Copilot and ask it to give me more
recommendations or compare data in a
different way.
This scenario might be very useful for
sales people working with Business
Central.
I'm traveling to London next week for my
customer meetings.
Maybe Copilot can help.
Copilot
is now accessing my uh calendar
and finding a meeting with my customer.
I have a meeting with Helen Ray from uh
Trey Research.
And that is actually happening at the
Microsoft London office.
I can ask Copilot to help me prepare for
that meeting.
And Copilot will pull data from Business
Central that are related to this
customer.
As you can see, Copilot prepared a sales
brief with some additional sales figures
and information I need for the meeting.
Uh discussed uh momentum of sales with
this customer and some account risk and
talking points, recommended talking
points that might be very helpful with
my conversations with with Helen.
But I have to get to that meeting uh and
I'm landing at Heathrow, so I need to uh
find my way.
Maybe Copilot can help.
Um I can ask Copilot about directions.
The meeting is at 2 Kingdom Street in
Paddington, so Copilot is very
confident I can get there on time. There
are various
public transportation options for me and
I have plenty of time
for maybe a short lunch.
I can actually ask Copilot about that.
But this will be so much outside of
Business Central area,
I will let you try that yourself in your
Business Central, in the new version of
Business Central with the new Copilot.
Thank you very much.